{
    "id": "b5985aa059da443893b893acbc4c1ac5",
    "title": "Prepositions Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This country is backward ………………….. many areas.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think that we can count ....................... him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t believe ………………….. ghosts. Do you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Beware ..................... . dogs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "off",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "During his regime, the king brought …………………. many radical reforms.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "about",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We are anxious ..................... . an end to this misunderstanding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "about",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is quite good ..................... .. remembering dates.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was green .................. envy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "My hands were blue .....................… cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We congratulated him ...................... his success.",
            "description": "On and for are both possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly he complained ………………….. chest pain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Contrary .....................… our expectations the central bank increased interest rates.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}